[BEA] Billy said I was a thief.
But she's the original thief herself!
[BILLY] Do you know what caused the fire?
[CLERK] No one knows, miss.
All I heard was that Mariela survived.
And so did her youngest daughter.
But her eldest daughter died.
[BILLY] But the father wasn't with them?
[CLERK] The rumor is that
Mariela's husband left her.
Ma.
I spoke with the lawyer.
She said it's possible
you'll be moved to a hospital.
You won't rot here anymore.
You can get out.
Which hospital?
The…
ward.
- Crazy. She's going to a psych ward.
- [MARIELA] Wait, the psych ward?
- What am I, crazy?
- [LAUGHS] She admitted it.
You want to be away from me, right?
- [WOMAN] It came from her.
- Ma, no. You're not crazy.
Ma, just think about it.
You'll be better off there.
You'll be taken care of.
Turns out she really is crazy.
- [WOMEN CACKLING]
- She belongs there.
- Ma. Hey, Ma!
- Hey!
- Let go of me! Ouch!
- Stop it, Ma!
- [WOMAN] Stay out of this!
- [BEA] What the hell?!
- Stop it!
- Ma! Ma!
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Ma!
- Come on.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
Happy second anniversary!
- Cheers, everyone!
- Cheers, guys!
- Oh, yes.
- Cheers!
[BLAIRE] Good thing those menaces are
behind bars now, chief.
Let's stop stressing out.
Right?
Let me join your group.
I can help.
Promise.
What help are you talking about?
I know someone.
He can give us new names
and a new life.
We can live as a different person
without anyone going after us.
Of course you need to let me in your group
and help me get out of here too.
Um, Billy?
Some of your stuff is still in my unit.
I'll just send it to you.
You know you can still stay there, right?
You just want to leave
as soon as possible.
No, it's all good. Thank you, Charm.
There's just too many of us.
My father is staying with us now too.
Thank you.
You're on good terms now?
He saved Oliver and Aunt Pres, so…
I owe him that.
Wow.
It's like you're
a different person already.
You know how to forgive now.
For your brother.
For Auntie Pres.
And for myself.
The CCTV technician will come tomorrow.
Yup, at 2:00 p.m.
I'll arrive at one.
- Okay.
- Me too, boss.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Bye, boss.
- Don't forget to lock the door.
Dude.
I thought you went home.
Um, I just wanted to ask something.
What is it?
Are we okay?
Yeah. What do you mean?
There's something you're not telling me.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Jordan, say it. Come on.
What is it?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Is it that obvious?
Jordan, please.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Right now? Um…
Shit. Okay.
I'll admit it.
Dude, I…
I'm in love with you.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[BILLY] Jordan,
say something.
Huh?
Is there any way we can lower the cost
of the additional security measures
you proposed?
Oh… that's all?
[CHUCKLES]
I thought…
Thought what?
Nothing.
Um, okay. I'll review it again.
Okay.
Sorry. I'm still talking about work.
No, it's okay.
I understand.
["PUZZLE" BY BELLE MARIANO PLAYING]
If only our partnership
with Peter had gone through.
We lost so much money, dude.
I think Claire will push through.
Dude, make sure you get enough rest.
Take care of yourself, okay?
["PUZZLE" CONTINUES]
Good night.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROWENA] Oh, thank you
for breakfast, my dears.
Oh, I mean brunch. [CHUCKLES]
I'll see you then.
[ROWENA GASPS]
Ralph.
Are you coming here for brunch
or to see your mom?
Um…
I-I just want to…
I just need to talk to you about Charm.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCOFFS]
Have you finally made up
your mind about that woman?
Yes. Yes, Ma.
[ROWENA] Good.
So,
are you here because you're
finally breaking up with her?
No.
She's the one breaking up with me.
Yeah.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you know what she told me, Ma?
She's willing to let me go
just so I can make up with you.
And Billy…
Billy agreed with her.
Because for her,
it's family first.
That's why I'm here now.
I'm sorry, son.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GRANADO] Hi, Billy.
I just got off the phone
with Attorney Reyes,
Bea's lawyer.
There was an incident in the city jail.
Bea's mother got into a fight.
She was provoked.
She flipped out, hurt others,
and she got injured.
Don't you think they just
made that up, Attorney?
Knowing Bea…
She's good at making up stories.
She did that to help grant her appeal
to transfer her mother
to a psychiatric facility.
[SIGHS] No. It really happened.
There was medical proof.
Attorney, I know Bea.
If her mother gets transferred
to the hospital,
it will be easier for them to escape.
If that happens,
they will be a threat to my family again.
That's it.
We can use that to counter Bea's appeal.
Let them know
that no matter what she and her mom do,
they won't be able to get out of jail.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Let me be clear.
Bea, Attorney Reyes.
You want to file an appeal
to transfer Mariela
to a psychiatric facility.
[SIGHS]
That's what I'm hoping for, Attorney.
My mother got hurt.
You know,
I wouldn't want her condition
to get worse.
We are prepared to prove that Mariela
should be transferred for her own safety
and the safety of others.
Let me just remind you.
We have strict laws when it comes to this.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
What law, Attorney?
Billy's Law.
Bea,
these laws are in place
to prevent people
from faking mental illness
to avoid punishment.
Wait.
Are you implying that my mom
is just faking it?
My mom wouldn't do that.
[SCOFFS]
She was confined
in a psychiatric ward before.
[GRANADO] Did she finish her treatment?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
All I'm saying is,
your appeal won't be granted easily.
My client and I will do
everything we can to oppose this.
We will demand a strict
competency evaluation.
I'm sure, Attorney Reyes, you know that.
Unless a qualified
mental health professional
certifies that Mariela is not competent
to stand in trial,
she has to stay in prison.
My client is willing to undergo
any evaluation, Attorney.
Wait, Attorney. What evaluation
are you talking about, huh?
Isn't it obvious?
This place isn't suitable
for my mom's condition.
The behavior shown by Mariela isn't
synonymous with legal insanity.
Without proof of total cognitive loss,
she can't get transferred.
You keep spouting all this stuff.
Synonymous, cognitive…
I don't care what it is.
Do whatever your client wants you to do.
But tell your client
that I won't back down.
I'm just clarifying your
and your mother's situation.
So you don't waste your time.
Oh, I'm not wasting anything!
I have plenty of time here.
I'll keep myself busy
fighting for my mother's rights.
Sure, that's your right.
But let me remind you
that my client is living a quiet life now.
And she, we, are determined
to keep it that way.
What did you say?
Your client is living a quiet life now?
Why? Is she happy?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA SCOFFS] Is she happy now?
Because her father is with them now?
They're like one
big happy family. Is that it?
[SCOFFS]
That's perfect.
Give your client my congratulations!
I hope they're having a blast!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's the real reason, Bea?
Why do you want to ruin my client's life?
I'm done here, Attorney.
For the US market,
we need a completely different
positioning strategy.
I want the brand messaging
to reflect momentum.
Something modern, emotionally direct,
but still premium.
That's why we are moving forward
with our new tagline,
"Real Love In Real Time."
- Oh.
- [CLAPPING]
[BLAIRE] Nice.
It communicates
urgency but not recklessness.
So the idea is,
meaningful connections,
intelligently matched,
delivered at the pace
people actually live today.
[CLAPPING]
So once everything is approved,
we will release it
on all of our social media platforms,
which are currently being prepared
by Val and Marj as we speak.
You can clap now.
- [CLAPPING]
- [TONI CHUCKLES]
Ralph.
You may want to add something?
- Uh…
Chief, looks like you're hiding
something from us.
Is Ralph going to invest in it too?
[CHARM] Hmm?
Well, I agree with
Billy's take on the US market
and how we will approach it.
The idea that life doesn't slow down.
Because if
you've set your mind on something…
[SIGHS, CLICKS TONGUE]
…you don't wait for the perfect time.
You choose the moment.
Because
real love…
Real love isn't just a feeling.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
It's a decision you make.
Right here.
Right now.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Okay. Um…
What I'm trying to say is
that even if
a lot of people are against us,
Charm…
will you marry me?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Um…
Ralph, let's talk first.
What?
Babe.
Didn't I tell you
to fix your relationship
with your mom first?
Babe, that's more important.
But I want to say yes,
knowing that she will be happy
with our decision.
I'll be the happiest
if you will say yes, dear.
My son said that
you're willing to let him go just
so that he can fix our relationship.
And Billy,
you never stopped telling my son
to always reach out to me.
Thank you
to you and Charm
for making me realize
that I've been wrong
and selfish.
Charm, I'm so sorry.
Daughter. [CHUCKLES]
Ralph, what are you waiting for?
Ask her again.
Okay.
- Uh…
- [CLAPPING]
Take… Take two?
- Take two. Okay.
- Take two.
- [ROWENA] You can do it.
- All right.
[ROWENA] Okay. Kneel. Do it properly.
- Uh, Charm.
- Mm?
[RALPH] Babe?
W-Will you marry me?
- Yes!
- [RALPH CHUCKLES]
Of course, yes!
Oh my God.
[ROWENA] Wow.
- [ROWENA] Son…
- Thank you, Ma.
- Oh my gosh!
- Happy family!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, guys.
- Congrats.
- Hi, Auntie.
- Thank you!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING]
THE COUNTRY'S NEWS
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
A HOUSE BURNED DOWN
ON SAN ISIDRO STREET
MOTHER LEFT INJURED
AND DAUGHTER DEAD
[KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING]
- Eric?
- Hi, ma'am.
How's the search for your other family?
The article's publisher
still hasn't wrote back to me.
I've also contacted the reporter
who wrote about the fire,
but I've got nothing.
I'm trying to follow up on them.
I've sent an email to another journalist.
But no one's answered.
They were caught in a fire too?
My eldest daughter died in that incident.
I go to her grave once in a while,
hoping that her mom
and sister would visit,
but…
And you found Billy's family first.
Does Billy know
that she has siblings other than Oliver?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't know how to tell her.
I don't want to hurt her.
I'm sure she'll get mad again.
Oh, Eric.
Aren't you tired of living a lie?
If I were you, I'd tell her everything.
Sure, she's going to get hurt,
but that's better than
lying to her forever.
[MUSIC BUILDS, FADES]
Pa, there's a fight back there.
- Let's go watch.
- I'll get going.
- Bye.
- Bye, Ms. Lucy.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
- Hurry!
Where are you going to take me?
Right out back. Let's go!
[OLIVER] There's a fight going on!
- [ENRICO] What is it?
- [OLIVER] Over there!
- Where--
- There's a fight!
- Auntie…
- [ENRICO] Wait up!
- Hurry up!
- Calm down.
Hurry!
Why--
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ENRICO EXHALES]
- Ta-da!
- [BILLY CLEARS THROAT]
Did you think we forgot?
[OLIVER CLAPPING]
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Dad.
[OLIVER] Make a wish! Make a wish!
Boom!
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
I'll take you
to Billy's favorite restaurant.
They serve seafood there.
Do you like seafood?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Okay. Let's go, Auntie Pres?
- [PRECIOUS] Mm.
- Okay, let's bring this.
- Let's box it up.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC STING]
Is everything ready
for Family Day?
[INMATE] We checked last night.
They replaced the railings.
You and your father are okay now?
Has he gotten his act together?
Happy and all together.
[OLIVER] Of course, Papa.
We won't be apart anymore.
I want to leave.
I can't take it anymore.
I just want you to reassure me
that Bea can't do anything else
to help herself and her mother.
Mariela still needs to undergo
psychiatric evaluation.
So Bea still has a chance of
getting what she wants?
What happened to us
was devastating.
But when I found out
that Dad didn't forget about me,
everything we had lost
didn't seem to matter anymore.
Because Dad came back to us.
[BEA] The truth won't hurt us.
It may even save us both.
I can request to speak to Billy, right?
I'm your lawyer.
Anything you intend to say to her
should go through me first.
I want to talk to her alone
and tell her myself.